<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="apply001">To be admitted to the Coles College of Business you must complete
        and submit a paper application form. The form is available as a pdf on the KSU website. 
        The three buttons below will help you with the application process. First, there is a 
        copy of the official INSTRUCTIONS for APPLYING to the COLES PROFESSIONAL PROGRAM. 
        The second leads to a tool that will calculate whether you meet the sophomore GPA 
        requirement. Third, there is an Admission Checklist tool that can you can use to 
        track your progress through the application process.</string>
    <string name="apply002">INSTRUCTIONS for APPLYING to the COLES PROFESSIONAL PROGRAM
        \n\n
        1. You must complete all parts of the application before you can submit it. You 
        cannot submit your form before all the necessary course grades are available in 
        your KSU online record. Your application will not be processed until after those 
        grades are official. (The Registrar\'s Office does not declare the grades official 
        until a few days after the deadline for their submission by the faculty.)
        \n\n
        2. Identify which rules for Coles admission you need to meet. This is determined 
        by your \"Catalog Term\". Your Catalog Term is initially the same as your \"Matriculation 
        Date\", which is the term you first took classes at KSU. However, you are required to 
        meet KSU\'s \"10-year rule\" - you must follow the requirements in a KSU Undergraduate 
        Catalog that will be no more than 10 years old when you graduate. If you are not 
        going to graduate within 10 years from when you started at KSU, you must move up to 
        a newer Catalog Term and follow the rules in the Catalog for that term. Also, if you 
        \"stop out\" for several terms, you will be required by KSU to move to the current 
        Catalog when you return.  Your Catalog Term can be found in your OwlExpress online 
        record. See an advisor for help on this point if you need it.
        \n\n
        3. Calculate whether you meet the Coles SOPHOMORE GPA REQUIREMENT.\n
        * A worksheet is provided to help you with your calculation. You must complete this 
        worksheet and submit it with your application.\n
        * The courses required and the GPA required have changed over time, so use the appropriate 
        Catalog Term to determine which rules you need to meet.\n
        * Check your online transcript to make sure you use the correct number of credit hours 
        you received for each course. Differences in credit hours will affect the GPA.
        \n\n
        4. Complete the OTHER REQUIREMENTS for admission described on the application form (total 
        hours, registration with Career Services, etc.), and complete the application form.
        \n\n
        5. There is a NONREFUNDABLE $100 APPLICATION FEE. Make sure you qualify for admission 
        before you apply! The fee must be paid at the Bursar\'s Office by CASH OR CHECK ONLY. 
        The bursar\'s Office is located in the Carmichael Student Center. You must obtain a 
        stamp or signature from the Bursar\'s Office in the appropriate box on the application 
        form, and also get a receipt.
        \n\n
        6. STAPLE a copy of the Bursar\'s Office receipt and the printout documenting your 
        Career Services registration to the back of your application form.
        \n\n
        7. TURN IN your completed application package to the Business Undergraduate Advising Center 
        on the 4th floor of the Burruss Building (BB 431). If no one is there, do not leave it, since 
        it it your evidence that you have paid your fee.
        \n\n
        8. After the Office for Undergraduate Business Programs has completed an administrative check 
        of your records, you will be notified by phone, email, and/or letter. Please respond promptly 
        to any comments regarding the need to submit additional documentation (substitutions, etc.).
        \n\n
        9. It is your responsibility to check with the Office for Undergraduate business Programs to 
        assure that all necessary actions have been taken so that your application can be processed.
        \n\n
        Revised 11/7/11        
        </string>
    <string name="applyGPA01">You must have at least a \"C\" grade in each of the required courses. 
        You must also meet the minimum GPA on the set of required courses. The calculation depends 
        on your Matriculation Date or Catalog Term.</string>
    <string name="applyGPA02">Elementary Applied Calculus - MATH 1106/1190</string>
    <string name="applyGPA03">Introduction to Financial Accounting - ACCT 2100</string>
    <string name="applyGPA04">Introduction to Managerial Accounting - ACCT 2200</string>
    <string name="applyGPA05">Principles of Microeconomics - ECON 2100</string>
    <string name="applyGPA06">Principles of Macroeconomics - ECON 2200</string>
    <string name="applyGPA07">Information Systems &amp; Communication - IS 2200</string>
    <string name="applyGPA08">Legal and Ethical Environment of Business - BLAW 2200</string>
    <string name="applyGPA09">Business Statistics - ECON 2300</string>
    <string name="applySummaryHead">Summary of Data Entered</string>
    <string name="applyCREDHRS">3</string>
    <string name="applyCredHours">Credit Hours: </string>
    <string name="applyGrade">Grade:</string>
    <string name="applyQualPts">Quality Points:</string>
    <string name="applyCatTerm1">Fall 2000 through Summer 2004</string>
    <string name="applyCatTerm2">Fall 2004 through Summer 2008</string>
    <string name="applyCatTerm3">Fall 2008 to present</string>
    <string name="applyGradeA">A</string>
    <string name="applyGradeB">B</string>
    <string name="applyGradeC">C</string>
    <string name="applyGradeNA">NA</string>
    <string name="apply004">Use this handy checklist to track your progress.</string>
    <string name="applyCheck01">Admission to Kennesaw State University</string>
    <string name="applyCheck02">Completion of at least 45 semester hours of college credit. Students 
        should have completed most of the required General Education courses for business students before 
        applying to the Program.</string>
    <string name="applyCheck03">Meeting with a Coles College of Business Advisor. (This app may help you 
        prepare for this meeting.)</string>
    <string name="applyCheck04">Registration with KSU\'s Career Services - register in the OwlLink system 
        from any computer anywhere - go to caeerctr.kennesqw.edu and login at the bottom of the page. After 
        completing your profile in OwlLink, go to the OwlLink home page, which will now show your name and 
        the date. Print out a copy of that page, with your name and date shown, and staple that printout 
        to the back of your application. If you are not currently enrolled in classes, OwlLink will not 
        let your register - you will need to get a letter from KSU Career Services Center, Room 2617 in 
        Kennewsaw Hall.</string>
    <string name="applyCheck05">Satisfactory completion of the courses in the Sophomore GPA Requirement. Refer to the GPA calculator.</string>
    <string name="applyCheck06">Complete application paperwork.</string>
    <string name="applyCheck07">Pay application fee and get Bursar\'s Office Stamp.</string>
    <string name="applyCheck08">Prepare application package.</string>
    <string name="applyCheck09">Turn in completed application package.</string>
    <string name="btnBack">Back</string>
    <string name="btnPlus">+</string>
    <string name="btnMinus">-</string>
    <string name="btnInstruct">Instructions</string>
    <string name="btnWorksheet">GPA Worksheet</string>
    <string name="btnChecklist">Admission Checklist</string>
</resources>
